streetauthority.com 2007-04-29

# StreetAuthority.com -- Privacy Policy

**_StreetAuthority.com Privacy Policy_**  
Last revised: December 2006

This Privacy Statement describes our privacy policy and explains what we do with the personal information that we collect from our users.

Your privacy is very important to us. StreetAuthority, LLC is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. Accordingly, we have adopted the privacy policy, based on the principles of notice, choice, access and security in the collection and use of all information regarding our subscribers and their activities at the StreetAuthority.com's web site. You can be assured of the following:

· We will not send you anything unless you opted-in to receive it. If you are receiving emails from us and you would like them stopped, login to your My Account page to manage your current subscriptions and DESELECT the check box labeled "Yes, I want to receive periodic notices, alerts and special offers that StreetAuthority believes can help me become a more profitable investor."

**What information does StreetAuthority.com gather?  
**StreetAuthority.com collects a limited amount of information about our newsletter subscribers to enable StreetAuthority to fulfill subscriptions. StreetAuthority may obtain the following information from its Registered Users and Subscribers:

1\. Registration and Subscription data  
2\. Site usage data

**1\. Registration and Subscription data.** The only individually identifiable information that StreetAuthority seeks about you is that which you are asked to provide when you register (for site access or you opt-in to our FREE newsletter) or subscribe to any "paid" subscription product the StreetAuthority may publish. This information may include your name, mailing address, e-mail address, and, in the case of a purchase, billing information. StreetAuthority uses registration and subscription information to maintain records about your use of our services, for billing purposes, and for us to occasionally send you information on products and services that we offer. THIS INFORMATION IS NOT SHARED WITH ANY THIRD-PARTY FIRMS, unless specifically stated or in other special situations described below.

**2\. Site Usage Data.** StreetAuthority collects non-identifiable information to measure how our registered users and subscribers use StreetAuthority.com's web site. This information may include statistics about the numbers and timing of unique visits to our web site(s), repeat visits, and which pages are viewed. We view this information to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Subscriber and Site Visitor Surveys**  
From time-to-time we may also conduct surveys, although you don't have to respond to them. This research is compiled and analyzed only on an aggregated (group) basis. We do this to better understand our users' needs and improve their overall experience when using our service. Your personal information and responses will remain strictly confidential, even if a third party conducts the survey. We may also notify you of a new product or new area of our site that we think may of interest you. If you'd prefer us not to contact you, simply visit your My Account page to manage your email options.

**StreetAuthority.com Email Referral Service**  
If you use our referral service to email one of our articles to a friend, you will need to provide us with your friend's email address. We will automatically send this person an email, attaching the recommended article and inviting them to visit and register with our site. We will not use these email addresses for any other purpose nor make them available to any third party.

**Online Advertising  
**StreetAuthority.com may display online advertisements from third party advertisers who are interested in reaching our audience. We may share with advertisers aggregated and non-identifying information about our Visitors and subscribers collected through the registration process as well as through any online surveys we may conduct. However, StreetAuthority.com will not share any personal information about any of its site visitors or subscribers with these advertisers.

**Email Marketing From Third-Party Advertisers**  
StreetAuthority.com may send out email advertisements or messages from third party advertisers to its site registration and subscriber lists. StreetAuthority.com will not sell or transfer to third parties the email addresses of its subscribers. StreetAuthority.com maintains strict confidentiality of its subscribers' email addresses. All site registrants and subscribers are given the opportunity of opting-out from receiving these promotional messages.

**StreetAuthority.com's Dedication to Data Security**  
StreetAuthority.com works to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems. The StreetAuthority cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party "hackers" from illegally obtaining this information.

**In the Event of a Change of Ownership**  
In the event of a merger or acquisition, the sales of the company or any change of ownership, all of StreetAuthority.com's customer information (including email addresses) may be transferred to a separate entity or entities. All StreetAuthority.com subscribers and registered users will be notified of any change in ownership, merger or acquisition of StreetAuthority.com's assets by a third party. Subscribers and users may choose to access and revise any of their registration and/or subscription information at that time.

**Where to Direct Questions About StreetAuthority.com's Privacy Policy**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact: Customer Service StreetAuthority.com, PO Box 83217, Gaithersburg, MD 20883-3217

**Revisions to This Policy**  
StreetAuthority.com reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner. Notice of any revision, amendment, or modification will be posted in accordance with the Internet Service Agreement.

USE OF THIS SITE SIGNIFIES YOUR AGREEMENT TO THE PRIVACY POLICY AND APPLICABLE USAGE AGREEMENT.

StreetAuthority.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time by posting a revised privacy policy on this web page. You can send e-mail to us with any further questions by visiting our Contact Us page. THANK YOU!
